const GOSPEL = {
    key: 'courseGospel',
    iframe: '<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GOaqUvXPBpU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>',
    questions: [
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '5:31',
            question: 'The gospel is not just how we get ***.',
            answer: ['saved']
        },
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '8:45',
            question: 'The gospel is not just the two great ***.',
            answer: ['commandments']
        },
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '13:35',
            question: 'The gospel is not the *** teachings of Jesus.',
            answer: ['moral']
        },
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '12:39',
            question: 'The gospel is ***.',
            answer: ['news']
        },
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '26:48',
            question: 'The gospel is ***-centered.',
            answer: ['god']
        },
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '30:29',
            question: 'The gospel is ***-centered.',
            answer: ['christ']
        },
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '33:24',
            question: 'The gospel is ***-centered.',
            answer: ['cross']
        },
        {
            type: 'FITB',
            time: '41:03',
            question: 'The gospel is ***-centered.',
            answer: ['grace']
        },
        {
            type: 'TF',
            question: 'The gospel is about being a good person.',
            answer: 'false'
        },
        {
            type: 'TF',
            question: 'The gospel being grace-centered means we are saved by believing in Jesus, not by living a good enough life.',
            answer: 'true'
        }
    ]
};

export default GOSPEL;
